( Theme music playing )
-( people shouting )
-( swords clanging )
-( dogs barking )
-( ravens cawing )
-( banging )
-( gasps )
( caws )
I've taken your castle.
-Theon?
-It's prince Theon now.
Get up. You have to get dressed.
I've taken Winterfell.
I took it. I'm occupying it.
I sent men over the walls
With grappling claws and ropes.
-Why?
-To take the castle.
-You went with Robb.
-And he sent me back to Pyke.
I'm a Greyjoy. I can't fight for Robb
And my father both.
-Where's hodor?
-I don't know.
Find the halfwit.
My men are bringing your people
Together in the courtyard.
Why?
So you and I can
Go down and tell them
-How you've yielded Winterfell to me.
-I won't.
Yes. you will.
I won't. I'll never yield.
We'll fight you
And throw you out.
( sighs )
The castle is mine.
But these people are still yours.
You'll yield to keep them safe.
To keep them alive.
That's what a good lord would do.
Think carefully about
What you want to say.
Theon.
Did you hate us the whole time?
-( thunder rumbles )
-( horse whinnies )
I've yielded Winterfell to Theon.
Louder.
Say prince Theon.
I've yielded Winterfell
To prince Theon.
You all know me.
Aye. we know you for
A steaming sack of shit.
Farlen. you be silent.
Listen to your little lord. farlen.
He has more sense than you do.
All of you should do as he commands.
My father has donned
The ancient crown of salt and rock
And declared himself
King of the iron islands.
He claims the north as well
By right of conquest.
You are all his subjects.
Bugger that. I serve the Starks.
-If you think you can
Hold the north with this...
-Shut up!
Theon:
If you serve me as loyally
As you served Ned Stark.
I will be as good to you
As he ever was.
Betray me. and you will
Wish you hadn't.
( crowd murmuring )
Maester Luwin. send a raven to Pyke
Informing my father
Of my victory here
And one to Deepwood Motte
To my sister.
Inform her that she's
To bring 500 men to Winterfell.
( crowd murmuring )
You are a maester of the citadel
Sworn to serve the lord
Of Winterfell. are you not?
I am.
I am the lord of Winterfell
As Bran just informed you.
Send the ravens.
My lord.
My Lord Greyjoy.
I see you've finally learned
How to address your betters.
What do you want?
I was brought here
A captive.
You were here the day
I was taken.
I'm the one who took you.
What of it?
Let me serve you.
Theon:
Serve me how?
I need fighters. not kitchen sluts.
It was Robb Stark who
Put me in the kitchens.
Put a spear in my hand again.
So you can bury it in my neck?
Do you take me for a fool?
Get up.
Step aside.
Why?
It's your dream. little lord.
The ocean has come
To swallow this place.
I ain't letting it drown me.
-And in a few days' time...
-Rodrik: Greyjoy!
Woman:
What have they done to him?
We caught this one on his way back
From Torrhen's Square.
Took out two of ours
Before I got his sword.
Ser Rodrik. it grieves me that
We meet as foes.
It grieves me you've less honor
Than a back alley whore.
You were raised here under this roof.
-These people are your people.
-They are not my people.
King Robb thought of you
As a brother.
My brothers are dead.
They died fighting
Stark men. men like you.
Aye. they died fighting
A war your father started.
Lord Stark raised you
Among his own sons.
Among them. but not one of them.
I was his hostage taken from my home.
If he were alive to see this...
He's not. He's dead.
The seven kingdoms are at war.
And Winterfell is mine.
I should have put
A sword in your belly
Instead of in your hand.
You've served this house
Faithfully. old man.
But keep talking and I'll...
( grunts )
Take him to the cells. Lock him up...
My prince.
You cannot let that stand.
He must pay.
I'll lock him in a cell
Until he rots...
No. he has to pay the iron price.
They'll never respect
You while he lives.
( thunder rumbles )
Ser Rodrik.
I sentence you to death.
No! You said no harm
Would come to them if I yielded.
The old man couldn't
Keep his mouth shut.
I urge you not to make
A hasty decision.
He disrespected me
In front of my men.
That was his decision. not mine.
He is worth more
To you alive than dead.
The Starks will pay.
Please. Theon.
Think what you do.
You'll address me as prince Theon
Or you'll be next.
Come.
No!
-No!
-Bran: Theon!
Please!
Ser Rodrik!
He who passes the sentence
Should swing the sword.
-Bran: I'm begging you!
-Coward.
Stop! Stop right now!
You don't give commands anymore.
Little lord.
-Please. stop this.
Please stop him.
-Rodrik: hush now. child.
I'm off to see your father.
Bran:
You said no harm would come!
You said no harm would come.
Theon. please.
Any last words. old man?
Gods help you. Theon Greyjoy.
Now you are truly lost.
Bran:
Theon. please. don't.
-Rickon: do something.
-Bran: I'll do anything. Please!
Rickon:
No. please. stop it!
-( grunts )
-( screams )
-( Bran wailing )
-( thunder rumbling )
( panting )
( wind howling )
Jon:
Ghost. stay with us.
Ghost!
There goes your pet.
Jon:
He's not a pet.
Qhorin:
You're right. he's not.
You can't tame a wild thing.
You can't trust a wild thing.
-Ghost is different.
-So you think.
Wild creatures have their own rules.
Their own reasons.
And you'll never know them.
Now the wildlings we're looking for
Sleep during the day
And hunt at night.
I thought you said
You couldn't know wild things.
I said you can't.
They find a nice cave
To hide in while the sun's up
And do their killing when it's dark.
-We could do the same.
-No. we couldn't.
This is their country.
They know where to walk.
Where not to walk.
I've lost good men
Who fell into a crevasse
They didn't see till they were in it.
My father always said
I'm of the north.
( chuckles )
-I wasn't joking.
-Look around. boy.
This look like home to you?
You start thinking
You know this place. it'll kill you.
You understand me?
No. you don't.
We're at war.
We've always been at war.
It's never going to end
'Cause we're not fighting an enemy.
We're fighting the north
And it's not going anywhere.
The watch has given
You a great gift.
You only have one thing
To give in return...
-Your life.
-I'll gladly give my life.
I don't want you
To be glad about it.
I want you to curse and fight
Until your heart's done pumping.
And know this. boy...
Your death will be a gift
For them south of the wall.
They'll never know what you've done.
They'll never know how you died.
They won't even know your damn name.
But they'll be alive because
Some nameless bastard
North of the wall
Gave his life for theirs.
Now. do you understand me?
I do.
You're even dumber than you look.
It's just words. boy.
To keep us a little
Warmer in the night.
Make us feel like
We've got a purpose.
( laughs )
Come on.
We've got to find these goat fuckers
Before night falls and they find us.
-Can you read?
-My lord?
Can you read?
This letter detailing
Our infantry movements
Was meant for Lord Damon
Of house Marbrand.
It was sent to Lord Marlyn
Of house Dormand.
My apologies. my lord. I must have...
Girl. fetch me
The "history of the greater
And the lesser houses."
It's the one on the...
( chuckles )
My cupbearer can read
Better than you.
To whom does
House Dormand owe allegiance?
My lord. I...
To the Starks of Winterfell!
Who have 20.000 men and my son!
I judged you might be
Good for something more
Than brutalizing peasants.
I see I overestimated you.
If you ever put my son's
Life at risk again. I'll...
Leave us.
Put the book away. girl.
( door opens )
( door closes )
Maybe you should devise
Our next battle plan while
You're about it.
( knocking )
( door opens )
Lord Petyr Baelish.
Mmm.
Give us the room.
Clear all this.
-Lord Tywin.
-Baelish.
-Wine?
-Thank you.
What news from the capital?
I traveled here directly
From Renly Baratheon's camp.
Ah. the late King Renly.
Rather a short reign.
Murdered by a woman. I hear.
So they say.
There has been talk
Of other forces at work.
Dark forces.
Here.
( scoffs )
Men love to blame demons
When their grand plans unravel.
It is my belief
That a moment of chaos
Affords opportunities
Lost soon after.
You say that as if you were
The first man alive to think it.
Yes. a crisis is an opportunity.
What other brilliant insights
Have you brought me today?
After the Lannisters and the Starks.
The tyrells command
The largest host.
Their lands are the most
Fertile in the seven kingdoms.
-feeding horses and soldiers.
-Yes. yes. yes.
The tyrells have not yet declared
For any of the surviving kings.
Loras wants revenge.
He blames Stannis for Renly's death.
And Margaery...
Wants to be queen.
Yes. she does.
House Tyrell rebelled
Against the iron throne.
-against my grandson.
-They did.
And perhaps that treason
Should be punished
One day.
After Stannis
And Robb Stark are defeated.
More wine for Lord Baelish.
If you will allow me to represent
Your family's interests.
I believe that
An advantageous agreement...
The Tyrell host has
Returned to Highgarden?
They have.
Pardon. my lord.
It's only wine.
You would ride there yourself?
Tonight. with your leave.
I'll have an answer by nightfall.
That'll be all. girl.
What else?
On your son Tyrion's directive.
I met with Catelyn Stark.
Why?
Littlefinger: he had
An interesting proposal for her
-concerning her daughters.
-Hmm.
-( groans )
-( shouting )
-A girl.
-A wildling.
-We could question her.
-You could.
She won't answer.
I've known a wildling to bite off
His tongue instead of talking.
-What's your name?
-Ygritte.
She was reaching for this ax
When you got to her.
Give her half a chance.
She'll bury it in your face.
I gave you my name.
I'm Jon Snow.
You ought to burn them you killed.
Qhorin:
We'd need a big fire for that.
Tell me. Ygritte.
Why do you want us
To build a big fire?
Are there some more
Friends in the area?
Burn them or maybe you'll
Need those swords again.
Our boy here's already
Killed one dead man.
He can do it again if he has to.
What waits beyond the pass?
-The free folk.
-How many?
( chuckles )
Hundreds and thousands.
More than you've ever seen. crow.
Why come to the mountains?
What's in the frostfangs
Your king could want?
Do you mean to march on the wall?
Do you know
Who I am. girl?
Qhorin Halfhand.
Tell me true.
If your people captured me.
Would they take me prisoner?
They'd take your head
Off your shoulders
If they was feeling kind.
If not. they'd kill you slow.
( sighs )
We have no food for her.
Can't spare a man to watch her.
Can't let her go. She'll bring
Mance Rayder's army down on us.
It needs to be done.
-Want me to do it?
-No.
No. I'll do it.
Come. brothers.
We'll leave him to it.
We'll meet you at the top.
Don't take too long.
We're deep in their country now.
( bird screeches )
You never killed
A woman before. did you?
You don't need to do it.
Mance would take you.
I know he would.
There's secret ways.
The crows would never catch us.
I'm as much a crow as they are.
Will you burn me...
After?
Can't.
Someone might see the smoke.
Strike hard and true.
Jon Snow.
Or I'll come back and haunt you.
That's cold.
Go on.
Be quick about it.
Do it.
Bastard. do it!
-( grunts )
-( clangs )
( breathing heavily )
( grunts )
( panting )
You can't do it. We both know it.
The sun's going down. Jon Snow.
-And your friends are nowhere close.
-I'll find them.
Call for them. Go on.
Call loudly.
Man:
May the seven guide
The princess on her journey.
( crying )
May the mother give her health.
May the crone give her wisdom.
May the warrior give her courage.
-( crying )
-( septon continues )
One day I pray you love someone.
I pray you love her so much.
When you close your eyes.
You see her face.
I want that for you.
I want you to know what
It's like to love someone.
To truly love someone.
Before I take her from you.
( septon continues )
( crying )
You sound like a little cat
Mewling for his mother.
Princes don't cry.
-I saw you cry.
-Did you say something. my lady?
My little brother cried
When I left Winterfell.
-So?
-It seems a normal thing.
Is your little brother a prince?
No.
Not really relevant. then. is it?
Come. dog.
Man:
Hail. Joffrey!
-Hail to the king.
-( man laughs )
Seven blessings on you.
Your grace.
Man:
Murderer! Bastard!
All hail the king.
Man:
He's no king. He's a bastard!
( people laughing )
Please. your grace. we're hungry.
( crowd shouting )
-Man: freak!
-Get the prince back to the keep now.
Yes. my lord. Come. quickly.
Woman: please. your grace.
Give us some food!
Man:
Bread. your grace. please!
-( groans )
-( crowd gasps )
Who threw that?
I want the man
Who threw that.
-Find who did that
And bring him to me!
-Man: hold on!
-Hold them back!
-Joffrey: just kill them!
Kill them all!
-Move. Move!
-Man: pull back!
Man:
Tear him to pieces!
What are you doing?
I want these people executed!
And they want the same for you.
( septon screaming )
( cheering )
Where's Sansa?
-( screaming )
-Man: through the door!
-( Growls )
-Man #2: come on!
( shouting )
-( whimpering )
-Protect the king!
-Get back!
-Fall back!
-Move!
-To the gates!
-Come in! Come in!
-Keep him safe!
-( crowd shouting )
-People: motherfucker!
-Watch out. Hold them back.
-Come on.
( whimpers )
-Hey!
-( laughs )
Traitors!
I'll have all their heads.
Oh. you blind. bloody fool.
You can't insult me.
We've had vicious kings
And we've had idiot kings.
But I don't know if
We've ever been cursed with
A vicious idiot for a king.
-You can't...
-I can. I am.
They attacked me!
They threw a cow pie at you.
So you decided to kill them all?
They're starving. you fool.
All because of a war you started.
You're talking to a king!
( shrieks )
And now I've struck a king.
Did my hand fall from my wrist?
Where is the Stark girl?
Let them have her.
If she dies. you'll never
Get your uncle Jaime back.
You owe him quite a bit. you know.
( panting )
-Where are you going?
-( cloth rips )
-( laughing )
-You ever been fucked. little girl?
-( whimpering )
-Come here.
Take some men
And go and find the Stark girl.
I take my orders from the king.
Man:
This way!
( screaming )
( sobbing )
Please!
No. no.
( screams )
( choking )
( grunts )
( Sansa breathing heavily )
Please!
You're all right now. little bird.
You're all right.
( crowd shouting )
( screams )
-Man: we'll get you. We'll get you.
-Man #2: this way.
-Are you hurt. my lady?
-The little bird's bleeding.
Someone take her back to her cage.
See to that cut.
-Well done. Clegane.
-I didn't do it for you.
He shouldn't make me wait.
The spice king is
The second wealthiest man in Qarth.
He makes everyone wait.
Of course. you could have
Avoided this embarrassment
If you married
The wealthiest man in Qarth.
I already have a husband.
Khal Drogo is gone. khaleesi.
You are far too young
To be a widow forever
And far too beautiful.
And you are far too smart
To think that I will
Succumb to flattery.
I have traveled
Very far in my life
And met many women.
But none that are
Immune to flattery.
-The mother of dragons!
-Ah.
Here he comes.
Forgive me.
I had terrible dreams last night.
Terrible dreams.
I could not sleep
Until the sun was shining
And the birds were singing.
Look what a beauty you are
Now the red waste
Has been washed off you.
I am sorry about
All that unpleasantness.
The silver hair of a true Targaryen.
Xaro Xhoan Daxos.
She is far too lovely
For a glorified
Dockworker like yourself.
Very true. and yet they say
That your grandfather.
Who sold pepper
Off the back of a wagon.
Married a lady far lovelier
And higher born than himself.
Every lady alive was lovelier
And higher born than my grandfather.
-( laughs )
-Daenerys: ahem.
Did my servants not offer you
Something to eat. to drink?
I'll have them flogged
In the square.
Thank you. my lord.
You are a gracious host.
But there is no servant alive
That can bring me what I want.
Oh. she has a talent
For drama. this one.
So. my little princess.
What is it you want?
My birthright...
The seven kingdoms of Westeros.
I fear I'm no better than
A servant in this regard.
I cannot give you what I do not have.
I'm not asking you for the kingdoms.
I'm asking you for ships.
I need to cross the narrow sea.
I need my ships as well.
I use them. you see.
To bring spices from
One port to another.
Whatever you grant me
Now will be repaid
Three times over when
I retake the iron throne.
Retake?
Did you once sit on the iron throne?
My father sat there
Before he was murdered.
But if you did not
Sit on it yourself.
Would it not be correct
To say take the iron throne?
I didn't come here to argue grammar.
Of course not.
You came to take my ships.
So let me explain my position.
Little princess.
Unlike you. I do not
Have exalted ancestors.
I make my living by trade.
And I judge every trade
On its merits.
You ask for ships.
You say I shall be repaid triple.
I do not doubt your honesty
Or your intentions.
But before you repay your debts.
You must seize the seven kingdoms.
-Do you have an army?
-Not yet.
You do not have an army.
Do you have powerful
Allies in Westeros?
There are many there
That support my claim.
When were you there last?
I left when I was a baby.
So. in truth. you have no allies.
The people will rise
To fight for their rightful
Queen when I return.
Ah.
Forgive me. little princess.
But I cannot make an investment
Based on wishes and dreams.
Now if you'll pardon me.
Do you know illyrio mopatis.
Magister of pentos?
Yes. we've met. A shrewd man.
For my wedding he gave me
Three petrified dragon eggs.
He believed... the world believed...
That the ages
Had turned them to stone.
How many centuries has it been
Since dragons roamed the skies?
But I dreamt that
If I carried those eggs
Into a great fire. they would hatch.
When I stepped into the fire.
My own people thought I was mad.
But when the fire burned out.
I was unhurt.
The mother of dragons.
Do you understand?
I'm no ordinary woman.
My dreams come true.
I admire your passion.
But in business. I trust
In logic. not passion.
I'm sorry. little princess.
I am not your little princess.
I am Daenerys Stormborn
Of the blood of old Valyria
And I will take
What is mine.
With fire and blood.
I will take it.
Yes. my lady. but not with my ships.
Who taught you to read?
My father. my lord.
Hmm.
I taught my son Jaime to read.
The maester came to me one day.
Told me he wasn't learning.
He couldn't make sense
Of the letters.
He reversed them in his head.
The maester said he'd heard
Tell of this affliction
And that we simply must accept it.
Ha!
After that. I sat Jaime down
For four hours every day
Until he learned.
He hated me for it. for a time.
For a long time.
But he learned.
Where is your father? Is he alive?
Who was he?
A stonemason.
A stonemason who could read?
-Hmm.
-He taught himself.
Quite a man.
What killed him?
Loyalty.
You're a sharp
Little thing. aren't you?
Did...
Forgive me. my lord.
I shouldn't ask questions.
No...
But you've already begun.
Did you know your father. my lord?
I did.
I grew up with him.
I watched him grow old.
He loved us.
He was a good man.
But a weak man.
A weak man who nearly destroyed
Our house and name.
I'm cold.
I'll fetch more wood
For the fire. my lord.
Mmm.
( horse whinnies )
( grunts )
Where are you going. girl?
The armory. my lord.
Why?
Lord Tywin sent me.
What might this be?
Lord Tywin gave it to me.
What for?
To take to the armory.
Why would he do that?
Let's go and ask him.
Move!
Get out of the way!
( men chatting )
Amory lorch.
A girl has named a second name.
A man will do what must be done.
Now!
A girl cannot tell a man
When exactly he must do a thing.
A man cannot make a thing happen
Before its time.
But he's going to tell Tywin.
He's getting away.
-It has to be now.
-( sighs )
Guard!
( horse whinnies )
-Your grace.
My honor. your grace.
Your grace.
-Your grace.
-Quent.
Lady Talisa.
Your grace.
I'm not sure I'm a lady.
Westerosi customs are still
A bit foreign to me.
It's hard to keep
All the rules straight.
But if I remember my lessons.
A woman of noble birth
Is always called a lady
Unless she's a queen or a princess.
I could find someone who knows.
Why are you so sure
I'm of noble birth?
Because it's obvious.
What if I told you my father
Sold lace on the long bridge
And my mother. my brother.
And I lived with him above our shop?
I'd call you a liar.
Not very noble to accuse
A lady of dishonesty.
I always thought
I was a brilliant liar.
Better at amputations. I'm afraid.
Quite a pretty spot.
Will we be here long?
I couldn't really discuss
Troop movements with you.
I'm not a spy.
Of course a spy
Would deny being a spy.
You're right. You've found me out.
I'm writing a letter
To the Lannisters.
"the young wolf is on the move."
Perhaps you'd join me...
If you've got time.
Of course. for. well...
Robb.
Mother.
Mother. this is Lady Talisa.
She's been helping with the wounded.
She's been very... Helpful.
Lady Talisa.
Lady Stark.
Lady Talisa...?
-Maegyr.
-Maegyr?
Forgive me. I do not know this name.
An uncommon name here.
An old name in Volantis.
Excuse me. my lady. Your grace.
I've missed you.
Yes. you look positively forlorn.
You surprised me. that's all.
I didn't think I'd see you today.
I wish that you were free
To follow your heart.
I know.
You have inherited your
Father's responsibilities.
I'm afraid they come at a cost.
-I know.
-You are promised to another...
A debt that must be paid.
-I haven't forgotten.
-Your grace.
My lady. News from Winterfell.
( wind howling )
Your brothers desert you?
I can tell you which way to go.
We'll stop here.
Too dark to go
Any farther today.
-Here? There's no shelter here.
-There's no shelter anywhere.
There is if you know where to look.
The cold could kill us both.
-If you light a fire...
-No fire.
-But a fire is...
Have it your way.
We'll stay warmer if we stay close.
Bet you freeze to death before I do.
Bet your life.
Think they're out looking for you?
-Yes.
-Think they'll find you?
Yes.
You're brave.
Stupid.
But brave.
We start again at first light.
Get some sleep.
Stop moving.
I'm just trying to get comfortable.
Stop it!
-You're still moving.
-Was I?
I didn't notice that time.
This cannot be true.
Bolton:
We've had ravens from white harbor.
Barrowton and the Dreadfort.
I'm afraid it is true.
Why? Why would Theon...
Because the Greyjoys
Are treasonous whores.
-My brothers?
-We've heard nothing of them.
( sighs )
But Rodrik Cassel is dead.
I told you. never trust a Greyjoy!
I must go north at once.
There's still a war
To win. your grace.
How can I call myself king
If I can't hold my own castle?
-How can I ask men
To follow me if I can't...
-You are a king.
And that means you don't have
To do everything yourself.
Let me go and talk to Theon.
There will be no talk.
He will die for this.
Theon holds the castle
With a skeleton crew.
Let me send word to
My bastard at the dreadfort.
He can raise a few hundred men
And retake Winterfell
Before the new moon.
We have the Lannisters on the run.
If you march all the way
Back north now. you'll
Lose what you gained.
My boy would be honored
To bring you prince Theon's head.
Tell your son
Bran and Rickon's
Safety is paramount.
And Theon... I want him
Brought to me alive.
I want to look him
In the eye and ask him why.
And then I'll take his head myself.
Why on earth would I trust the word
Of a lying little savage like you?
I'm no liar.
All wildlings are liars and savages
With no loyalty
To anything or anyone.
I done what I had
To do to stay alive.
I hate the Starks as well as you do.
Let me serve you. my lord.
How? And don't tell me
To put a spear in your hand.
There are other ways
To serve. my lord.
I'm a prince now. and you'd do well...
There are other ways
To serve. my prince.
( chuckles )
Like what?
We know things. the free people.
You know things?
Like what?
How to eat dirt?
( laughs )
( scoffs )
Other things.
Savage things.
Wait outside.
I always wondered
What you had under there.
It comes at a price.
I'm not killing you.
That's your price.
I already had that.
What do you want. then.
Other than your miserable life?
What all free people want...
My freedom.
Well. you shall have it. then.
But only if you serve me well.
-Ow.
-Shh.
-It's not deep.
-I thought they were
Going to kill me.
They thought so. too.
He hated me. the man who hit me.
I saw it in his eyes. Hated me.
He never met me before.
But he wanted to hurt me.
-Of course he did.
-Why? Why would a stranger...
You are everything
He will never have.
Your horse eats better
Than his children.
It doesn't matter now. He's dead.
I would have given them
Bread if I had it.
I hate the king
More than any of them.
Don't say these things.
If the wrong people hear you...
But you're not the wrong people.
Don't trust anybody.
Life is safer that way.
( murmurs )
And where are you going?
I have something for you
From prince Theon.
-What?
-Me.
He says I'm to make the rounds.
And keep you warm.
( groans )
( whistles )
( panting )
The spice king refuses me
Because I'm a bad investment.
The silk king won't support me
Because of his business with
The Lannisters.
Why offend his best customer?
And the copper king
Offers me a single ship
On the condition that I lie
With him for a night.
Does he think I will
Whore myself for a boat?
When I came to this city.
I had nothing.
Truly nothing.
I slept by the docks.
And when I could find
Work loading the ships. I would eat.
If not. I dreamed of food.
Today I am the richest man in Qarth.
Do you think the path
From poverty to wealth
Is always pure and honorable?
I have done many things. khaleesi.
That a righteous man would condemn.
And here I am. with no regrets.
Bar the gates. Ring the bells.
Slowly. khaleesi.
-( bells tolling )
-( people shouting )
Where are they?
Where are my dragons?!
( dragons screeching )
( theme music playing )